fullofthings.com 2012-10-25

# FullofThings - Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

###  General

FullofThings.com as a local classifieds site publishes posted information. By posting content in FullofThings.com, the user understand and agrees that such content is public and accessible by any third party and that it may appear in results of search engines (such as Google, Yahoo!, MSN ), and other search engines. We reserve the right to change this policy should we deem it advisable to do so.

### Information collected

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information to facilitate your usage, and for other purposes like ascertaining the number of visitors to our web site

We use cookies to keep track of what is your preferred local site, as well as to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

Our servers are located in the United States. Therefore, if you choose to provide us with personal information, you are consenting to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers in the United States. In the process of registration, we collect and store the following personal information:

  * email address
  * physical contact information (e.g. zipcode), which enables us provide users with information on how to find ads close to them

### Third parties 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. On this website, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to this website's users based on their visit to this website and other websites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by Google by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy at: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

### Disclosure

We don’t sell or rent or provide users’ personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without users’ explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other’s rights, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety.

### Access and modification

You may change your personal information at anytime by logging into My Account on FullofThings.com.
